A Guide to the C. Sterling Hutcheson Papers, 1925-1969
Library of Virginia
- Subject Files
  - Professional
    - College of William and Mary - Education Committee Meeting, 1966 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 224)
    - College of William and Mary, 1966 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 225)
    - College of William and Mary - Honorary Degree, 1968 June (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 226)
    - College of William and Mary, 1967-1969 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 227)
    - College of William and Mary - Photographs - Charter Day, 1963 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 228)
    - College of William and Mary - Photographs - Commencement, 1963 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 229)
    - College of William and Mary - Photographs - Commencement, 1968 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 230)
    - College of William and Mary - Photographs, 1962, 1966, n.d. (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 231)
    - College of William and Mary - Printed material and reports (includes financial and budget statements and reports; also some curriculum propositions re. advanced degrees) (Box-folder Box 10)
    - Virginia State Library, 1961 June - 1962 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 232)
    - Virginia State Library, 1963 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 233)
    - Virginia State Library, 1964 January-June (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 234)
    - Virginia State Library, 1964 July-December (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 235)
    - Virginia State Library, 1965 January-June (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 236)
    - Virginia State Library, 1965 July-December (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 237)
    - Virginia State Library, 1966 January-June (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 238)
    - Virginia State Library, 1966 July-December (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 239)
    - Virginia State Library, 1967 January-June (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 240)
    - Virginia State Library, 1967 July-December (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 241)
    - Virginia State Library, 1968 January-June (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 242)
    - Virginia State Library, 1968 July (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 243)
    - Virginia State Library, 1968 August-December (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 244)
    - Virginia State Library - VSL Survey, 1968 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 245)
    - Virginia State Library, 1969 January-June (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 246)
    - Virginia State Library, 1969 July-December (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Personal
    - A.P.V.A., 1956-1964, 1966 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 248)
    - Arnold [family], 1961, 1963 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 249)
    - Mrs. W. R. Baskerville, 1960 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 250)
    - Beagles, 1957-1967 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 251)
    - Book Reviews [by CSH], 1959-1961, n.d. (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 252)
    - [Boydton, history of], 1964 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 253)
    - Buggs Island Property, 1945, 1950-1955, 1962, n.d. (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 254)
    - Willie T. Bullock, 1961-1962, n.d. (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 255)
    - Aaron Burr records, 1960 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 256)
    - [Civil War] 1861-1865, 1949, 1955-1956, n.d. (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 257)
    - Joint Civil War Centennial Commission, 1960-1965 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 258)
    - D.A.R., 1961-1962, 1964 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 259)
    - Colonel William Davies, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 260)
    - England, 1953, 1960-1961 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 261)
    - [Episcopal Church] - Ad Hoc Committee, 1960-1962 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 262)
    - [Episcopal Church] - Committee for Study of Possible Nominees for Suffragan Bishop for Diocese of Southern Virginia, 1958-1960 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 263)
    - [Episcopal Church] - St. James Church, 1955-1961, n.d. (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 264)
    - [Episcopal Church] - St. James Church, 1962-1964 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 265)
    - [Episcopal Church] - St. James Church, 1965-1968 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 266)
    - [Episcopal Church] - West Mecklenburg Cure, 1964-1965, 1968 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 267)
    - [Genealogical Inquiries], 1948, 1950-1951, 1953-1956, 1958-1960 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 268)
    - [Genealogical Inquiries] - F. L. Hutcheson, 1948, 1954, 1958-1960 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Highway Deptartment, 1961-1962 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 270)
    - [Historical documents - photocopies and transcripts] (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 271)
    - Huntley-Witt-Snead letters, 1961-1962, n.d. (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Jamestowne Society, 1959-1961, 1963-1964, 1967 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 273)
    - The Magna Carta Commission, 1964-1965 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 274)
    - [John Marshall 200th Anniversary of his Birth], 1955 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 275)
    - [John Peter Mettauer] (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 276)
    - Prestwould, 1964-1966, 1968 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 277)
    - Sons of the Revolution, 1948, 1958 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 278)
    - U. D. C. Speech on Jefferson Davis, 1962-1964, 1969 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 279)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (VALC) - Highway Markers, 1962-1963 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 280)
    - VALS - Public Defender, 1964-1965 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 281)
    - VALC - Recidivist Statutes, 1966-1967 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 282)
    - Virginia Historic Landmarks Commission, 1965-1967, 1969 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 283)
    - Virginia Historical Society, 1951-1962 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 284)
    - Virginia Historical Society, 1963-1969 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 285)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, 1961 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 286)
    - White Lecture, 1961-1962 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 287)
    - Farm Files - Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 288)
    - Farm Files - Land Use Plan, 1943 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 289)
    - Farm Files - Loose Papers, 1925-1949 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 290)
    - Farm Files - Loose Papers, 1950-1959 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 291)
    - Farm Files - Miscellaneous Papers before 1954 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 292)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1954 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 293)
    - Farm Files - Old Accounts, 1957-1960 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 294)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1959 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 295)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1960 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 296)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1961 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 297)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1962 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 298)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1963 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1964 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1965 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1966 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 302)
    - Farm Files - Accounts, 1967 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 303)
    - Farm Files - Account Books, 1956, 1960 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 304)
- Writings
  - By C. S. Hutcheson (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 305)
  - Probably By C. S. Hutcheson (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 306)
  - By Others (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 307)
  - Ephemera/quotations (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 308)
- Printed Material
  - General I (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 309)
  - General II (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 310)
  - With Information About Or By CSH (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 311)
  - Historical Places (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 312)
  - Portrait Unveilings/in memoriams (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 313)
  - Presentation Copies of Writings and Speeches (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 314)
  - Professional Newsletters/Congressional Record (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 315)
  - Programs (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Reprints (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Acts, 86th Congress, 1959 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 309)